-警察  -《芝加哥警署》前情回顾
- Police! - Previously on Chicago PD...
斩首  那是贩毒集团独有的手段
Beheading-- that's a signature cartel move.
亚德勒斯·迪亚斯  外号"八爪"
Adres Dias, aka Pulpo.
开门
Open up!
警员中枪
Officer shot!
站住
Stop!
是你在背后搞的鬼
You played games.
退后  博伊特
Back up, Voight.
是你把她害死了
And you got her killed!
这是我搭档的血
That's my partner's blood.
安东尼奥  有人带走了迪戈
Antonio, someone's taken Diego.
快点  安东尼奥
Come on. Go, Antonio.
米切尔  让他进来  让他进来
Mitchell, let him in, let him in.
-劳拉  -安东尼奥  安东尼奥
- Laura! - Antonio...Antonio!
天哪
Oh, God.
我们儿子  他肯定吓坏了
Our baby.He's got to be so scared.
我一定会救他回来的
I will get him back.
我知道  你必须救他
I know you will. You have to.
现在有什么线索
What do we know?
后巷里没监控
There's no cameras in the alley.
我们正在查两边街道上自动取款机的监控记录
We're checking the streets on both sides for ATM video.
街坊呢
Neighbors?
一位女士说看到一辆白色货车
One lady gave us a white van,
但是不知道牌照和司机样貌  没有线索
but no license, no driver description, nothing.
警探们在查了  各小队也在挨家挨户
Detectives are rolling, squads are canvassing the area
询问盘查  看看能不能找到监控录像
and knocking on doors, checking for cameras.
警方监控那边也有人去查了
Someone's on the PODS right now.
我们前面有监控  但是后巷什么都没有
We have security cameras out front, but nothing in the alley.
我知道
I know.
-劳拉女士  劳拉女士  -先生
- Para Laura, para Laura! - Sir--
放他进来  放他进来
Let him in. Let him in!
午夜放了"八爪"  否则你儿子没命
"Pulpo free by midnight, or your son dies."
我儿子在哪里
Where's my son?
反正不在这里
Uh, I know he's not here.
除此之外
Beyond that--
别让我问第二遍
I don't think you want me to ask you again.
好吧  好吧
Ah, si, si, si, si.
波哥大  哥伦比亚首都
我在波哥大听说过这种事
I heard about this type of thing back in Bogota.
你儿子被绑架了  对吗
Yeah. Your son was kidnapped, yes?
对的
Yes.
我看到过很多类似的消息
Yeah, I read that many times.
很多  很多
Many, many times.
如果满足绑匪的要求
If the kidnappers were given what they wanted,
那被绑走的妻子
then the wife
或者儿子就会被释放
or son was returned,
毫发无损的回去
not a single scratch on their faces.
你应该满足绑匪的要求  安东尼奥
Maybe you should give 'em what they want, Antonio,
不论他们要什么
whatever that may be.
如果你还想再见到迪戈的话
If you want to see Diego again, that is.
-你好  艾琳  -艾米  利亚姆
- Hi, Erin. - Emmy, Liam.
你们好
Hey, guys.
你爸爸在家吗
Is your dad home?
爸爸  艾琳来了
Hey, dad! Erin's here!
-怎么了  -亚历克
- Yeah? - Alec?
你们俩先到里面去好吗
Hey, you guys want to go inside?
-好的  -去吧
- Okay, yeah. - Okay.
-拜拜  艾琳  -拜拜
- Bye, Erin. - Bye!
茱尔斯
Jules...
他们抓了安东尼奥的儿子
They took Antonio's son.
在我看来  就是抓了我儿子
And they took my own, as far as I'm concerned.
不惜一切代价救回迪戈
Nothing else matters till we get Diego back.
不惜一切
Nothing.
警长
Sarge...
事件起因是雷夫和库珀被斩首
So this all started with Rev and Coop getting their heads chopped off.
他们两个在"八爪"手下的工作是一样的
And both did essentially the same job for Pulpo,
都是中级毒品分销商  对吧
mid-level distribution, right?
也就是说"八爪"在清理门户
So we know Pulpo's cleaning house.
通常把旧家具扔掉后会怎么做呢
And what do you do when you get rid of old furniture?
你得买新的
You got to bring in something new.
这个人很有戏
This guy stood out.
欧内斯托·米帕斯
It's Ernesto Milpas.
芝加哥警署在09年抓到他时  他负责
He was running 15 corners between 22nd and Kedzie
22大街和凯基大道间的15个街角售毒点
when CPD pinched him in '09.
对  我记得  当时我跟茱尔斯也参加了抓捕
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I was on that bust with Jules.
他去年刑满出狱了
He was released last year.
这个人一心想往上爬
He was a climber.
可能他正期望升迁呢
Maybe he's looking to get promoted.
这是坏人中最好的选择
He's the best of a lot of bad options.
目前收集到了多少他的资料
What do we have on him now?
从邮局找到他的地址了  不过是一年前的
P.O.'s got an address. That's a year old.
奥林斯基  奥林斯基
Olinsky, Olinsky!
怎么了
Yeah?
我们走
Hey, let's go, man.
我做好拿下那个混蛋的准备了
I'm ready to nail this son of a bitch.
我们首先得打扮好
First we gotta get dressed.
你来选一件吧
You can just pick one.
好吧  这件案子我们主要负责
All right, now, our job on this one
那地方的前期监视
is to put early eyes on the place
同时提供支援
and then provide backup as well.
明白
Roger that.
温迪来电
你未婚妻吗
Fiancee?
对
Yeah.
你跟她说过了吗
Have you talked to her?
还没说
No, not yet.
她现在还不知道你的工作吗
She still doesn't know what you do?
你上次刷牙是什么时候
When's the last time you brushed your teeth?
我的身份是流浪汉
I'm supposed to be homeless, man.
流浪汉就不刷牙吗
That's not a good excuse.
-好  给你们118  -谢谢  警长
- Okay, you guys have 118. - Thanks, Sarge.
阿特沃特和伯吉斯  452号车
Atwater and Burgess, car number 452.
452?
怎么了
What?
-今天你俩跟着我  -是  长官
- You two with us today. - Yes, sir.
走吧
Come on.
道森
Dawson.
有什么需要
Look, whatever you need,
尽管来找我
you have my support.
谢谢  长官
Thank you, sir.
我们聊一下
Let's talk.
好吧  怎么回事
All right, look, what's going on?
基本上  他在全部门的人面前指控
He basically accused me of getting Willhite killed
说是我害死了威尔海特
in front of the entire district.
就是他害死的
No basically about it.
你这会儿应该待在监狱里的  博伊特
You're on the wrong side of the bars right now, Voight.
他们把你想要的职位给我了
Yeah, what does that say about your police skills
这足以说明你的工作能力了吧
if they gave me the job you wanted?
够了  拜尔登  出去走走
Quite enough. Belden, go take a walk.
汉克  我希望你不要太震惊
Hank, I hope this don't shock you,
但确实有些人觉得
but there's some people who think
你不配重新得到这个职位
you don't deserve to be back on this job.
关我什么事
What do I care?
现在你已有一名部下殉职
Well, so far, you got a dead cop
还导致一名儿童遭绑架
and an abducted kid as a legacy.
如果再不扭转局面  你的地位就难保了
This is gonna be a real short stint if you don't turn things around.
-452号车吗  -是的
- 452? - Yep.
好的
Okay.
老天  什么...
Oh, God. What...
不  你怎么得罪普拉特了
Oh, no. What did you do to Platt?
我没怎么着她啊  你怎么得罪她了
I didn't do nothing to platt. What did you do to Platt?
你肯定是得罪她了
You must have done something.
伯吉斯  我现在提醒你
Burgess, I'm gonna tell you this right now.
不要执迷不悟
Don't walk down a road you can't come back from.
好吧
Okay, fine.
我骂她是鼷鼠了
I called her a house mouse.
不是吧
You didn't.
为了她表弟的俗戒指
She ran me all over creation
她使唤我到处跑  然后她...
for this gaudy ring of her cousin's, and then she...
抱歉
I'm sorry.
有时我的脾气会影响我的沟通能力
Sometimes my temper can hinder my ability to communicate.
我不知道安东尼奥是怎么熬过来的
I don't know how Antonio's handling all this.
如果我的孩子被绑架  我会失去理智的
If I had a kid snatched up, I would be incoherent.
我以前觉得博伊特手下的人是战无不胜的
I used to think that cops under Voight were invincible,
结果茱尔斯牺牲了
and then Jules died.
我当时还握着她的手
I was holding her hand.
你当兵的时候都是怎么面对这种事的
As a soldier, how did you deal with it?
一般来说...
Generally...
要为那些无辜的人报仇
Take it out on those who didn't deserve it.
来啊来啊  快来
Come on. Come on, come on, come on.
老天  你都不出声  当忍者啊
Jeez. What are you, a ninja?
你好歹出个声啊  伙计
You gotta make some noise or something, man.
-有什么发现吗  -还没
- Anything? - No.
-钱拿来  -逗我呢
- Money. - You kidding me?
拿来
Come on.
好吧  我只有20块
All right, all I got is a 20.
以后要还的
I want that back later.
她会以为你劈腿了
She'll think you're having an affair.
不会
Nah.
我告诉她  他们把我从学院调出来
I told her they pulled me out of the academy
去局里做文书工作了
to do paperwork in the ivory tower.
这个借口好
Ah, that's original.
我不想让她担心
I don't want her to worry.
长痛不如短痛  孩子
End it now, kid.
这样可以不用遭受痛苦绝望的人生
Avoid a lifetime of misery and despair.
继续掏你的垃圾箱去吧
Go find another garbage can, huh?
是他
That's him.
目标出现
There's our boy.
鲁塞克在搞什么
What the hell is Ruzek doing?
站住
Freeze!
所有人行动  行动
Everybody, go, go!
妈的  站住
Damn it, freeze!
嫌疑人从仓库西南方逃走了
Suspect is on foot out the southwest side of the warehouse.
我出来了啊  他已经逃走了
Coming out! He's in the wind.
你还好吗  孩子
Hey. You okay, kid?
我没事  我是个笨蛋  但我没事
Yeah, I'm fine. I'm an idiot, but I'm fine.
这不是你的错  真的
Hey, it wasn't your fault. Trust me.
没有任何迪亚戈出现过的迹象
No sign of Diego that he was ever here.
我们都看到他了  你搞什么呢
We had him! What the hell was that?
-我行动了而已  -别激动
- Hey, I made a move. - Take it easy.
-你搞砸了  -别激动  放松
- A stupid one! - Take it easy, take it easy.
别忘了是谁让她负责的
Let's not forget who let herself get jumped!
喂  我...
Hey, I...
道森警探  我是伯吉斯
Detective Dawson, this is Burgess.
你最好来看看这个
You're gonna want to see this.
我们走  走吧
Let's go. Come on.
告诉我你有发现了
Tell me you have something.
翻译出来
Translation.
你敢叫  我们就割掉你的舌头
Scream, and we cut out your tongue.
爸爸
Daddy.
他们说要杀了我  爸爸
They say they're gonna kill me, daddy.
看后面的墙板
Check out the paneled wall.
不是这里
That's not here.
我需要那些哥伦比亚人所搭的那班飞机上
I want lists of the other passengers
其他所有乘客的名单
on the planes the Colombians arrived in.
国土安全局会有完整的名单
Homeland Security will have it all.
我们可以查查和"八爪"一起来的其他人
Maybe some others came in with Pulpo we can run down.
我知道这违反了我们的基本原则
I know this goes against everything we stand for.
我们应该考虑跟他们做交易
We should consider making the deal.
用"八爪"换迪亚戈
Give them Pulpo for Diego.
安东尼奥
Antonio.
他是我儿子  博伊特  我们接受交易吧
He's my son, Voight. Let's make the trade.
交易解决不了问题  老兄
Trades don't work out, bro.
上级也不会同意
No one above would okay it.
我该相信你说的哪个借口
Tell me which one of those excuses I'm supposed to believe.
我们还有时间
We still have time.
仔细查看这些资料
All right, go through these one by one.
看有谁和"八爪"还有欧内斯特有关系
See if anyone crosses with Pulpo or Ernesto.
这些是我的
These are mine.
记住  带红标的文件
Okay, look, remember, the red-tabbed files
是已经入过库的公共信息系统文件
are the CIS that have been paid out, okay?
不能...  喂  不对不对
And you ca--hey, no. No, no, no, no.
那些不是同一类的
Those don't go in that pile.
必须分开放  不然都会
You gotta keep it separate, or you're gonna get it confused
-被弄混的  还有你  -吉恩
- with the other ones, and you-- - Jin!
-刚刚才说过  -吉恩
- Told you-- - Jin.
什么事
Yeah?
录像上有什么发现吗
What you got so far on the video?
好的  录像是昨晚录的
Okay. It was recorded last night.
芝加哥警署罪犯
白人女性
逮捕罪名  偷窃  暴力殴打  非法持有大麻
化名或曾用名  艾琳·林德赛
音轨上可以听出远处还有其他声音
There are some other voices in the distance on the audio track,
因此可以推断视频是在公共场所拍摄的
so there's reason to believe that it was in a public place.
可能是酒吧的内堂或者是汽车旅馆里
Back room of a bar, maybe a motel.
但是没有什么确实有用的线索
It's really not much to go on, though.
谢谢
Thanks.
霍斯特德  琳德赛  过来一下
Halstead, Lindsay, come here a sec.
我们也许会考虑进行交易
In case we're gonna consider a trade,
你们先去查看一下这几个地点
I want you to check out these locations.
最佳视线  狙击位置  建筑构造之类的
Sight lines, sniper spots, the works.
你在考虑谈判吗
You considering negotiating?
先去查查
Just check it out.
好
Okay.
-博伊特  -什么
- Hey, Voight. - Hmm?
我看错鲁塞克了
I was wrong with Ruzek.
是啊  他没有遗传到他父亲太多优点啊
Yeah, he certainly ain't his father's son.
我是凭直觉选的他
Yeah, it was a gut call.
我判断错了  我要把他送回警校
I was wrong, so I'm gonna send him back to the academy.
埃尔文  你的直觉一向比你可靠
Your gut's always been smarter than you, Alvin.
还需要吗  这还有
You need more? Here.
安东尼奥  我想向你道歉
Hey, listen. Antonio, I want to apologize.
把迪戈救回来后再说吧
Save it, for when we get Diego back.
行
Sure.
你的秘诀是什么  兄弟
So what's your secret, man?
什么秘诀
To?
手下有这么多线人
Keeping so many CIs.
绝不要求他们出庭作证
Never make them testify,
绝不对他们撒谎
and you never lie to them.
有时为了保护线人
Sometimes you gotta be willing to toss a case,
得甘愿放弃案子
protect an informant.
这样在你需要他们的时候
'Cause sometimes when you really need someone,
他们才愿意为你赴汤蹈火
they're still there for you.
道森警探  没想到会收到你的短信
Detective Dawson, surprised to see your text.
谢谢你的回信
Yeah, thanks for hitting me back.
-出什么事了  -就是平时那些事
- Hey, what's wrong? - The usual.
听着
Listen.
你还记得欧内斯托吗
Do you remember Ernesto?
在搜查26号街与索耶街路口的房子时
He was caught up in the net when we busted
我们逮捕了他
that house on 26th and Sawyer.
-当时你在那里工作  -我记得他
- You were working there. - Yeah, I remember him.
他偏好褐色卷发的女子
Curly-haired brunettes. So that was his thing.
他被释放了
Yeah, well, he's back on the street.
我想知道在最近几周时间里
I need to know if he's ordered any girls
他有没有找什么女孩
in the last couple of weeks,
我最关心的是  他可能在哪里藏身
but what I really want to know is where he might be flopping.
我可以去打听打听
I can call around.
-真的吗  -没问题
- Would you? - Yeah.
你能  我是说
Can you, you know--
是的  好
Yeah, yeah.
你从来都不拐弯抹角
You always played it straight with me.
-有消息就跟我联系  -好
- Call me if you get anything. - Sure.
这事很急
I need it fast.
好好好  我知道了
Okay, okay, I got it.
你没事吧
Hey, are you okay?
欧内斯托
This Ernesto --
我八岁的儿子失踪了  他和此事相关
My eight-year-old son is missing, and he's involved.
所以事关重大
So it's important.
我的天  很遗憾
My God, I'm so sorry.
听着  我会帮你打听的
Hey, listen, I will call around.
谢谢你  贾斯敏
Thank you, Jasmine.
顺便告诉你  我的真名是维多利亚
My real name's Victoria, by the way.
我知道
Hmm. I know.
好  在那里和那里都安排狙击手
All right, put snipers there and there.
那扇窗子后面也安排两名狙击手
And two more snipers in the windows there.
好的
Yeah, okay.
怎么了
What is it?
你知道绑架案中交易成功的几率是多少吗
Do you know what percentage of kidnappings end in a successful swap?
不到1%
Less than 1%.
只是偶然事件而已
It's just a contingency.
-我有事要问你  -问吧
- I gotta ask you something. - Go ahead.
我看到你的档案了
I saw your file,
你做博伊特的线人时的档案
as one of Voight's CIs.
是他找你做线人的吗
Did he turn you out?
根本不需要他找我
He didn't have to turn me out.
他救了我一命  所以我自告奋勇的
I volunteered because he saved my life.
什么事
Yeah.
二号线上有你的电话
You've got a call holding on line two.
艾丽卡·格拉迪沙尔
An Erica Gradishar?
回头我再打给她
I'll call her back.
她说有重要的事找你
Said it's pretty important.
我会打给她的
I'll call her back.
贾斯敏来电
抱歉  我不是很想进去
Hey, sorry. I didn't want to go in there.
没事  我明白
No, I get it.
我打听了欧内斯托的事
Okay, so I asked around about Ernesto,
有几个姑娘去西亚当斯街上的波尔克酒店
and a few girls visited him, some other Colombians
招呼过他和其他一些哥伦比亚人
at the Polk Hotel on West Adams.
谢谢你  真是太感谢你了
Thank you. Thank you so much.
安东尼奥  希望你平安救回你儿子
Antonio, I hope this turns out okay.
西亚当斯街上的波尔克酒店
Polk Hotel on West Adams.
这人住哪个房间
Where's this guy's room?
他被关在这里过
He was here.
我儿子在哪里
Where's my son?
滚远点  快滚
Get outta here. Run!
他知道  安东尼奥
He knows, Antonio.
尽力而为吧
Do what you gotta do.
动手吧
Do it.
我儿子到底在哪里
Where the hell is my son?
我要律师[西语]
Abogado.
不  这里可没有律师  伙计
No, ain't no lawyers around here, ese.
在警察到来前  你还有三分钟
You got about three minutes till this alley's full of uniforms.
做你该做的
Do what you gotta do.
我会先戳瞎你一只眼
I'll start with an eye.
把他的眼挖出来
Cut his eye out!
挖
Do it!
-动手啊  -快说
- Do it. - Come on!
快说啊
Come on!
第二次了  欧内斯托
Second time, Ernesto.
你的罪名可不小
You're looking at life.
我们可以说是八爪找的你
But we can say that Pulpo came in,
威胁你  然后强迫你去帮他们的
threatened you, and forced you to help them out.
我要律师
Abogado.
不  不
No, no!
我们要谈的是我儿子
We're gonna talk about my son!
迪戈  他才八岁
Diego! Eight years old!
在我家乡  是不能那样的
Where I'm from, that's off-limits.
我要律师
Abogado.
怎么说呢
I don't know.
真庆幸我不是安东尼奥
I'm glad I wasn't Antonio back there.
你呢
You?
我希望我是
Oh, I wish I was,
因为我清楚的知道我会怎么做
'cause I know exactly what I would have done.
我要求交换  拿你换迪戈
I want to talk about the trade, you for Diego.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
看来你们那边事情不顺啊
Things aren't going too well, hmm?
首先  我要一架私人飞机送我去波哥大
I'm gonna need a private plane to Bogota, to start.
不可能
That's impossible.
这还只是我第一个条件呢
That's just to start.
需要帮忙吗  警探
Help you, Detective?
没事  谢谢警督  如果你不介意
I'm fine, thanks, Lieutenant. If you don't mind...
我介意
I do mind.
看来你们得先统一意见才行啊
Sounds like you guys need to get your ducks in a row.
我很同情你的遭遇  安东尼奥
I appreciate what you're going through, Antonio.
真的  但是就暴力犯罪这一项
I mean that, but violent crimes
这人身上就背了好几条人命
has multiple murders on this guy.
他之前从你手中逃脱了刑事处罚
He beat your rap before.
我觉得你现在的情绪不适合处理这个案件
I just don't think you're in the right head space for this.
他就在这儿
He's in here.
-爸爸  -宝贝
- Dad. - Hey, baby.
你还好吧
Hey. How you holding up?
我现在想都不敢想那件事
Not even thinking about that right now.
你们怎么来了
What are you guys doing here?
我们在家里一分钟都待不下去了
We couldn't sit at home another minute.
到底是怎么回事  你知道什么消息吗
What's happening? What do you know?
你们能把伊娃和加布里埃拉带到舒服的地方
Can you guys take Eva and Gabriela
休息一下  尽可能满足她们的需要吗
somewhere comfortable, get them whatever they need?
放心吧
You got it.
我们谈谈
Let's talk.
给你
Here you go.
谢谢  但是我一点都不饿  真的
Thanks, but I'm not hungry, really.
你们有什么消息了吗
What have you guys heard?
我们不能说
Nothing we can say,
我只能说整个芝加哥警署正在竭尽全力
other than the whole CPD is doing everything it can.
我和迪戈说的最后一句话是他很烦人
The last thing I told Diego was that he was annoying.
他做了什么
What was he doing?
用一把乐购玩具枪对我发射激光弹
Shooting laser bullets at me with a Lego gun.
我们会找到他的
We'll find him,
然后在接下来的若干年  他还会一直烦你
and he's gonna annoy you for years to come.
我保证
I promise.
我也希望如此
Yeah, I hope so.
博伊特处事的方式很不同
Voight's got a different way of doing things.
-和你的不一样  -是的
- Not your way. - No.
那他有主意对吗
But he's got some ideas?
他会一些技巧
He has some techniques.
可能会有用
They might help.
作为你的妻子
As your wife,
我喜欢这样的你
I love the man that you are.
你就是我心中的好父亲
You are the father I expect you to be.
伊娃和迪戈每天都会感受到这点
Eva and Diego see that every day.
但作为一个母亲
But as a mother...
你不择手段也要把我们儿子带回来
do whatever it takes to bring our son home.
我们用你的方法来处理吧
Let's do it your way.
你麻烦大了  伙计
You got a big problema, ese.
我要律师
Abogado.
这里可没有律师  伙计
No comprende abogado down here, bro.
我想[西语]
Espero.
等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait.
原来你会说英语啊
You speak english after all.
我什么都没干
No, I-I didn't do anything.
不不不  太晚了
No, no, no, no, no. It's too late.
你要知道安东尼奥打人可是奥林匹克水准的
You know Antonio was gonna fight in the Olympics.
我没伤害他  求你们了  别
I didn't hurt him. Please, no.
别  别
No, no.
他这点权利还是有的
He's still got a hell of a right.
别别别
Aah, no, no, no, no!
我的搭档因你而死
My partner is dead because of you,
现在我儿子也出事了
and now my son.
等等  等等  手下留情
Wait, wait! Please.
他的名字是马泰奥  他的名字是马泰奥
His name is Mateo. His name is Mateo.
求你了  我有他的手机号  求你了
Please, please! I have his cell number, please.
求你了  别打我
Please, no!
求你了
Please.
是马泰奥抓了你的小儿子
Mateo has your young son.
求你了  求你了
Please, please.
[西语]
他跑了  没有迪戈的信息
He's running. Nothing about Diego.
我定位了他的手机  这样跟西亚当斯塔
I've pinged his cell to the West Adams tower,
还有城市中心就形成了一个三角形
triangulating with the city center.
我要城市所有
I want men deployed
主要的交通路线上都有我的人
to all major transportation routes out of the city--
中途机场  奥哈拉机场  包括所有高速公路
Midway, O'Hare, I'm including all expressways.
他在联合车站
He's at Union Station.
所有人  去楼下
Everybody, hit the floor.
大家四散搜索
Everyone, fan out.
他一定就在这里
He's gotta be here somewhere.
爸爸  爸爸
Papa, papa!
-路易斯  -爸爸
- Luis! - Papa!
我看到他了
I see him.
印第安纳波利斯
在上一辆开往印第安纳波利斯的车
Boarding a bus for Indianapolis.
等着我们
Wait for us.
中美巴士公司第949号车上客
Mid-America Bus Number 949
目的地印第安纳波利斯
is now boarding for Indianapolis.
中美巴士公司第949号车上客
Mid-America Bus Number 949
目的地印第安纳波利斯
is now boarding for Indianapolis.
你敢叫  我就杀了你
You scream, I'll kill you.
然后再去你家杀了你父母
Then I'll go to your house and kill your parents.
明白了吗[西语]
Comprende?
琳德赛看到他了
Lindsay has eyes on him.
他们在开往印第安纳波利斯的车上
They're on a bus headed to Indianapolis.
迪戈没有受伤
Diego is unharmed.
芝加哥警察  你们经理办公室在哪
CPD. Where's the manager's office?
车上有多少人
How many on the bus?
带驾驶员25个
25 plus the driver.
-你能联系上驾驶员吗  -塔莉娅·库克
- Can you contact the driver? - Talia Cook.
可以  我有她的手机号
Yeah, I got her cell phone number.
-她够冷静吗  -我不知道
- Can she handle herself? - I don't know.
-我们才共事一年  -把号码给我
- Only been with us a year. - Give me the number.
我是塔莉娅
This is Talia.
塔莉娅  我是经理办公室的克林特
Talia, this is Clint in the manager's office.
我车上有个警察
I got a cop on this bus.
我知道
I know.
芝加哥警署的人想跟你说话
CPD here wants to talk to you.
你好  塔莉娅
Hey, Talia.
我叫安东尼奥
My name's Antonio.
听着  我们需要你假装
Listen, we're gonna need you to pretend
客车的发动机出故障了  告诉乘客
there's some engine trouble and announce that
后面会有辆客车来接管他们
a second bus is coming behind you to take over.
你以前遇到过发动机故障吗
You ever have engine trouble before?
有一次
Once.
冒出来很多烟  然后发动机失灵了
There was a whole lot of smoke, and the engine conked out.
好的  就像那样  只是没烟而已
All right, well, it's just like that minus the smoke.
我好像看到他了
I think I see him.
好的  你要冷静
All right, you gotta play it cool.
轻踩几脚刹车  然后路边停车
Just tap your brakes a few times and pull over.
剩下的交给我们  你能做到吗  塔莉娅
We'll do the rest. Can you do that, Talia?
是的  警官  我现在就停车吗
Yes, sir. You want me to do it now?
等十分钟以后
Just give us ten minutes.
是的  警官
Yes, sir.
发信人  沃伊特
十分钟
你们要把客车逼停到路右边
You gotta push it all the way over here to the right.
发动机似乎出故障了  乘客们
Looks like we're having engine trouble, folks.
我需要靠边停车看看情况
I'm gonna pull the bus over and take a look.
就是这辆
There it is.
我已经请求另一辆大巴来接你们了
I've already called another bus to take you on your way,
很快就会过来
so it should be here in a minute or two.
别着急
Don't worry.
后备巴士开来了  乘客们
Here comes the backup bus now, folks.
我对造成的不便表示抱歉
Apologies for any inconvenience.
我们对耽误大家深感抱歉  乘客们
All right, we're real sorry for the delay, folks,
但我们又派了一辆没有问题的大巴
but we've got a tried and true new rig out here
会立刻将各位送达目的地
that'll get you where you're going right away.
现在  我需要大家下车
Now, what I need from all of you
拿好各自的行李
is to disembark, grab your luggage,
然后有秩序地登上后面那辆大巴
and head on over to the next bus in an orderly fashion.
各位能做到吗
Can you do that for me?
谢谢
Thank you.
站起来啊
Get up.
-能瞄准吗  -不行
- Do you have the shot? - Negative.
-你好  -你好
- Hey. - Hey.
发动机是什么故障啊
So what happened with the engine?
-还挺吓人的  -发动机只是...
- Pretty scary, huh? - The engine just--
后面那辆车不会再有什么事了吧
Is everything gonna be all right back there?
我们都能按时到站  对吗
We are gonna get where we need to go on time, right?
当然  当然
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-没问题的  -好的
- It's gonna be fine. - Okay.
因为第二辆车看起来...
'Cause the second bus is looking...
听着  我家里还有孩子
Listen, I got kids at home.
警察[西语]
Policia.
[西语]
放下武器
Drop it!
-迪戈  -放下武器
- Diego! - Drop it!
我发誓我会杀了他
I swear I will kill him.
把枪放下
Put it down.
-能瞄准吗  -不行  他有掩护
- Do you have the shot? - I don't. He's not clear.
-把枪放下  -我可不这么想
- Put it down! - I don't think so.
-放下枪  -开枪啊  来啊  开枪啊
- Drop the gun. - Shoot! Come on, shoot!
来啊  我发誓我会杀了他
Come on. I swear I'll kill him.
你要开枪吗
You gonna shoot?
我可不觉得
Nah, I don't think so.
琳德赛  扶稳
Lindsay, hold on to something.
过来  我抱住你了  趴下来
Come here, I got you. Get down.
安东尼奥  我抱住他了  抱住迪戈了
Antonio, I got him! I got Diego, I got him.
-他没事  过来吧  -迪戈
- He's okay. Come here. - Diego.
-爸爸  爸爸  -过来  过来
- Daddy. Daddy! - Come here, come here.
你刚才太勇敢了
Oh! You were so brave.
你太勇敢了  儿子  太勇敢了
You were brave, buddy. You were brave.
你做得很对
You did the right thing.
把手放进口袋里
Put your hands in your pockets.
这样会好些
It gets easier.
没事了
It's okay.
你没事的
You're okay.
对不起  车里味道太大
Sorry about the smell.
我根本不在乎
I don't mind a bit.
迪戈  迪戈
Diego? Diego.
-天呐  -妈妈
- Oh, my God. - Mom!
天哪
Oh, my God.
我还以为再也见不到你了呢
I thought I'd never see you again.
我爱你们
I love you guys.
我非常非常爱你们
I love you so much.
-嘿  -这么晚才到家
- Hey. - You're home late.
你怎么还没睡
What are you still doing awake?
等你啊  我给你发短信了
Waiting for you. I tried texting.
是吗
You did?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我一定是调了静音
I guess my ringer was off.
你看起来很疲惫
You look tired.
我看起来疲惫
I look tired?
-你看起来很漂亮  -工作怎么样
- I think you look beautiful. - How was work?
区里买了新电脑
Well, district got these new computers.
上面让我们把案件档案录进去
They want us to input case files, and --
-肯定快把你搞疯了  -是啊
- It must drive you crazy. - Yeah.
你总有一天会出外勤的
You'll be out of that office someday.
-你想吃点什么吗  -当然
- You want something to eat? - Sure.
我有点通心粉可以热一下
I got some pasta I can heat up.
太好了
Great.
-你还记得吉姆·卡弗蒂吗  -不记得
- Do you remember Jim Cafferty? - No.
我们在隆特拉烧烤见过他一次
You met him once when we were at Frontera Grill.
他想给他妈妈去年秋天
Anyway, he wants to get a write-off
买的船办报废手续
for this boat his mother purchased last fall.
所以他到办公室来
So he comes into the office,
而我不得不给他解释
and I have to tell him that the only way
只有当他把这艘船用作商业用途
he can do that is if he's using it
或者作为第二住所时才能这样做
for business purposes or as a second home.
我们刚才出去转悠  多买了一个这个
We were out and about and had an extra one of these.
这是什么
What's this?
真的假的
Oh, are you kidding?
热狗餐厅买的  那队得排一个多小时呢
Hot Doug's? That line is like an hour.
Hot Doug's是芝加哥最有名的小吃店
以鸭肝热狗和鸭油薯条闻名
是啊
Don't we know?
波兰香肠热狗
The Elvis?
说真的  伙计们
Oh, seriously, you guys.
这是给我的  你们不用这么客气
This is for me? You didn't have to do that.
他们不用这么客气
They didn't have to do this.
他们不用  真的
They didn't. Really?
-真的  -那好
- Yes. - Okay, then.
-你猜怎么着  -怎么
- You know what? - What?
你们两个好像需要换一辆巡逻车了
You guys look like you could use a different squad car.
这是651号车的钥匙  归你们了
Here are the keys to 651. All yours.
谢谢您  警长
Thank you, Sergeant.
我们对您感激不尽
Yes, how can we ever thank you?
小事一桩
Don't mention it.
走吧
Let's go.
真是大快人心啊
That's a nice sight to see.
是的  长官
Yes, sir.
指挥官
Commander...
罗恩  你告诉过我
Ron...you told me
如果我想要管理情报组
I'm gonna have to learn to deal with politics
就需要学会处理政治问题
if I want this job in intelligence.
那么
Well...
这就是我的处理方法
this is me dealing with it.
拜尔登警督和我只能选一个
It's Lieutenant Belden or me.
你想让我和他成为一丘之貉
You gonna handcuff me to the likes of him,
我宁可回监狱里去
I may as well be back in my jail cell.
我已经得到许可按照我的方法
I've been given the go-ahead to run intelligence
-来管理情报组  -全体警官
- the way I want to run it. - Officers!
-立  正  -没人干扰
- Atten--tion! - No interference.
现在这是我们的队伍了
This is our unit now.
敬  礼
Present arms!
你们按我的方法做事
You do things my way,
我们的方法
our way,
每天下班后你们会知道自己做了正确的事
you'll unclip your badge at night knowing you did right.
茱莉·怀特
在你们身边的警察
The police standing next to you
是你们的亲人
are your family.
对我来说
And to me,
没有什么比这更重要了
there's nothing more important.
如果你们愿意加入
If you're in,
就跟着我
stay here with me.
我已经等了三十分钟了
I have been waiting for 30 minutes.
你去找我的指挥官干什么
What the hell are you doing, going to my commander?
我不知道你是怎么从监狱里出来的
I can't speak to how you got out of prison.
关键证人被发现死亡  对吗
Key witness was found dead. Is that right?
差不多吧
Something like that.
但是  我知道你是怎么复职的
I am informed, however, in how you got reinstated.
你应该是内务部
You were supposed to be
用来抓住重要罪犯的一条渠道
a pipeline for I.A. into some heavy hitters,
但你至今还没让我们有任何收获
but you haven't given us a damn thing.
莫里斯·欧文斯的五千块
5,000 for Maurice Owens.
我很快就会对他下手的
I'll make a move on him soon.
别用"很快"搪塞我
Don't jerk me off with "Soon".
你为我工作  汉克
You work for me, Hank.
你为我工作
You work for me!
明白吗
Do you understand?
我为芝加哥工作
I work for Chicago.
你明白吗
You understand?
芝加哥
Chicago.
看看这景色
Look at that.
我记得我小学的时候
I remember when I was in grade school,
老师给我们读过一个故事
the teacher read us a story
是很久以前一个很有名的作家写的
by some precious little writer from a long time ago.
我记得他好像是英国人
I think he's English or something.
他来旅游后批评了这个地方
And he was bagging on this place after visiting here.
你知道他管它叫什么吗
Know what he called it?
他管它叫"野蛮人居住的城市"
He called it "A city inhabited by savages."
我说行动的时候我们再行动
We move when I say we move.